

Ajay Kumar SK

Full Stack Developer

Contact

Address

Chennal, India 600119

Phone

6380765665

E-mall

smilyboy2207@gmail.com

Unkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in /s-k-ajay-kumar-6750582

Skills

Content Marketing

Web development projects

Programming

Decision-Making

Flexible and Adaptable

Training and Development

Problem-Solving

Self-starting and resourcefull intern with experience implementing front-end and back-end coding. Astute and always-learning designer of user interactions on websites and databases that are sound and easy to use. Proven problem-solver with solid grounding in data-driven applications and concepts. Communicates clearly with technical and non-technical team members and promotes drive for customer service.

Work History

2023-11 -

Full Stack Web Developer Intern

2023-12 Intern. Chennai

I am expert in html and ass and I also learn know the language python, java and a programming

Education

2022-11 -

Current

B. Tech: Information Technology

Agni College of Technology - Neelankarai

Interests

I am interested to apply to your company and I give best potential to grow your company